# Sadi Luis Alberto Rueda

# Full Stack Web Developer

Correo: sadiluisrueda.94@gmail.com | Cel: +543435363040

https://www.linkedin.com/in/sadi-luis-alberto-rueda-fullstack/ https://github.com/SadiLuis https://sadi-rueda-dev.netlify.app/

Full Stack Developer with Front-end orientation, + 1 year of experience in the industry working with technologies such as React.js, Node.js, Firebase and others. In my last job I worked as a junior Full-Stack Developer, performing layout and bug fixing tasks.

Many people refer to me as a talented, creative, empathetic and great team player, advanced to my seniority, always ready to share knowledge and with initiative.

# **Technologies**

HTML, CSS, Javascript, React.js, Redux, Node.js, Express, Firebase, MongoDB, Typescript, SQL, PostgresSQL, Tailwind, GIT, SCRUM. | LEARNING: Jest, C#, .NET, Angular.js, Next.js, Chakra-UI. |

# Professional Experience

### Full Stack Developer - Anlak | June 2022 - December 2022 | Remote

- Technologies used React.js |Typescript | Firebase | Node.js
- Modification and creation of multiple functionalities in Back-end.
- Connection between Back-end. Front-end and Firebase.
- Creation and implementation of functionalities and user experience.
- Investigation and solution of bugs, both in Front-end and Back-end.
- Learned technologies : Jest | Css-Sass

### <u>Full Stack Teaching Assistant - Henry Bootcamp | September 2021 - March 2022 | Remote | </u>

- Lead a group of students to achieve their integration in the study team.
- Assist in the resolution of exercises and promote group collaboration (Pair Programming).
- Propose ideas for the improvement of the Bootcamp processes.
- Provide technical guidance on doubts or questions about the languages taught in the Bootcamp.

### **Projects**

# Social-Media-App

# Personal Development App | December 2022

- Technologies used React.js | Firebase | Chakra-UI
- Front-end made in React.js with 100% Chakra-UI layout.
- Use of Firebase to Create, Manupulate and Read user data in real time.
- Goal: To understand in depth in a better way Firebase, apply new concepts learned from Chakra-UI.
- Deploy ( https://social-media-appreact.web.app/ )

### Netflix-clone

# Personal Development App | November 2022

- Technologies used React.js | Firebase | Tailwind
- User interface creation based on Netflix's original model using React.js and Tailwind.
- Creation of Registration and Login for users through Firebase.
- Deploy (https://netflix-clone-react-2ab91.web.app/)

### Chat.

# Personal Development App | August 2022 Technologies used React.js | Firebase | Tailwind

- Group chat where several people can communicate at the same time.
- Simple interface made in React.js and Tailwind.
- Google login through Firebase and its real-time communication for messages between users.
- Deploy (https://chat-react-76b11.firebaseapp.com/)

### Simple Login

# Personal Development App | August 2022

- Tecnologias usadas React.js | Node.js | MongoDB | Chakra-UI
- Login simple realizado en React.js y Chakra-UI con una página de inicio simple donde el usuario puede registrarse e iniciar sesión.
- Almacenamiento y Autenticación en Firebase.
- Deploy (https://login-react-9b927.web.app/)

### E-commerce MOBI ATR

# Front-end Programmer | May 2022 - June 2022

- Project Leader | Analytical skills | Peer Mentor | Integrate new ideas.
- Technologies used React.js | Node.js Express.js | SQL Postgressql | Css
- Final project to conclude the programming bootcamp done among 8 programmers.
- Front-end and back-end connection. Creation of user records and login for users.
- Implementation of styles for the user interface.
- Database modeling.
- Deploy ( https://mobi-app.netlify.app/ )

# SPA Dogs Api

### FullStack Developer December 2021 - January 2022

- Technologies used React.js | Node.js Express.js | SQL Postgressql | Css
- Development of a SPA with temperament filtering, search bar, alphabet sorting, creation of new dogs, tabs with the image of the dogs and details of each one.
- Front-end developed with React and Redux, styles made in pure Css.
- Back-end developed in Node.js implementing Express and the database implemented with PostgresSql and Sequelize.

# **Education**

# Bootcamp Henry | https://www.soyhenry.com |

Start: September 2021Completed: May 2022

#### Universidad del Litoral

**IComputer Engineering** 

Start date: 2021 - 2022

# <u>Languages</u>

Spanish: NativeEnglish: B1-B2